EDWIN AU

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER | PRODUCT DESIGNER

https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eaudesign



416-880-3791



edwinau@rogers.com



PROFILE I'm a web developer first but wear multiple hats with experience in product design and graphic design. I'm passionate about modern and intuitive applications that put user experiences first. I own the ability to pin-point shifts and provide solutions to the ever changing market needs. Feel free to contact me to find out how my skills can benefit your team.

EDUCATION



Web Development Immersive

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

- > Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp
- > Complex object oriented programming
- > JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, AJAX, SQL, SASS, HAML.



B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

Sep 1998 - April 2002

> Skills in marketing, trend analysis, merchandising and graphic design.

HIGHLIGHTS > Strong presentation & communication skills. Experienced with R&D.

Central Saint Martins (UK)

Experimentation Design Course

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

> Selected by Ryerson University to partake in this foreign exchange program.

- > Complex graphic design tasks.
- > Thesis: Triple bottom line & green design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

■ RendezYou

Front End Developer, Web Designer ① Mar 2017 - Present

https://rendezyou.herokuapp.com

- > Working as Web Developer for RendezYou, a web app that neatly tucks itself into the online travel and tourism sector.
- > Built on JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, HAML, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, SQL.
- > Stretch goal reached: RendezYou is fully responsive for desktops, tablets and mobile devices.

Disney Consumer Products

Product Developer ② Nov 2013 - Apr 2016

www.dcpi.disney.com

- > Provided creative leadership in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Canada.
- > As one of five designers working out of Disney Canada's head office, I guided 50+ licensees on product design ranging from apparel and home accessories, to toys and arts & crafts. These products were widely sold at Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Dollarama, Canadian Tire, just to name a few.
- > My regular work day can range from approving product designs online, to traveling and meeting with vendors communicating Disney design goals, objectives, initiatives and milestones.
- > Researching market analysis, trend forecasting (15%); Managing/coordinating (35%); Implementing (40%); Reporting (10%).

■ Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy)

Associate, Graphic Designer ② Sep 2012 - Sep 2013

- > Having accumulated 10 years of product development experience in Toronto -I decided to take my skills as a Technical Designer, Fashion Designer, and Product Developer abroad, ending up with the opportunity to work at Dolce & Gabbana's head quarters in Italy Milan for a year, helping their design and sales team with preparation and sales of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections.
- > Achievements: Creating the Fall 2013 sales deck (external) and Spring 2014 employee training material (internal) for the fashion house. For more information please visit https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing
- > This in-house experience allowed me to see design through a European lens. My daily tasks include utilizing my design skills, photoshop skills, and provide light market analysis to the design/sales team.

SKILLS























